dreammoods.com 2018-10-04

# Dream Moods: Privacy Statement

** **

We, at [Dream Moods](http://www.dreammoods.com/index.html), recognize your right to confidentiality and has created this privacy statement to disclose the information gathering and dissemination practices that we employ.

**Information Automatically Logged** : When you visit DreamMoods.com, your IP address is automatically logged. The IP address is used to gather broad demographic information, to diagnose possible issues with our server and to administer and monitor our site.

We use Google Analytics to provide information of where in the world users are coming from and how they are finding the site.

**Advertisers:** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Most of our third-party advertisers use cookies to help serve targeted online advertising. Cookies received with ads are collected by the ad companies themselves; we do not have access to this information.

As our partners, the below mentioned advertising companies have legitimate interests to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP addresses and cookie IDs from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via the below email addresses.

   Conversant, Inc's [privacy policy](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy) \- [feedback form](http://www.conversantmedia.com/feedback?t=g)

   Exponetial Internative, Inc's [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) -  [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com)

   Index Exchange's [privacy policy](http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/) \- [feedback form](http://www.indexexchange.com/contact/)

   Rhythm One's [privacy policy](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy#rhythmonelink) \- [privacy@radiumone.com](mailto:privacy@radiumone.com) 

   Sovrn Holdings, Inc's [privacy policy](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/). - [privacy@sovrn.com](mailto:privacy@sovrn.com)

**Personal Information:** Certain information you voluntarily submit to Dream Moods may be displayed on the site as a way to help others and increase interactivity. We also look at the information and review it an an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who visit our site. Our goal is to customize and personalize our web presence. 

We do not disclose your personal information except if required by a subpoena or court order. We do not sell, trade or share your email addresses to any third parties or provide any information that allows you to be personally contacted.

**External Links:** This site contains links to other sites. Dream Moods is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these web sites. 

**Public Forums** : This site features several discussion forums that are available to all visitors.  We try to minimize the personal information that we need from you. When you register for an account, you will need to provide us with a username, password, and an email address (which you can keep hidden from public view). Any other information you provide in your personal profile (i.e. photo, full name, messenger handles, location, etc) is optional and will be publicly viewable. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas immediately become public information and is accessible by anyone.  Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information or any information for that matter.  

Note also that when using the discussion forums, a "cookie" will be placed on your computer's hard drive. This cookie will identify your browser when you visit the site again. You may set your browser to refuse cookies. However the forums will not function properly if cookies are disabled. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection:** Dream Moods is not intended for children under age of 13.  No one under 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use the discussion forums. We do not and will not intentionally maintain information about anyone under the age of 13. We regret any inconvenience this may cause. If you are a parent and are aware that your child is a member in our forum, please email [forums@dreammoods.com](mailto:forums@dreemmoods.com) to have their account terminated.

**Contacting The Web Site** : If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [privacy@dreammoods.com](mailto:contact@dreammoods.com).
